dude your posture is
jacked internal
rotation
kyphosis do you even
lift okay I want you to breathe for me
can you do
that okay dude you're breathing as
and you're doing this for 24 hours a day
7 days a week can you imagine how bad
this is for your
body
wow uh okay you got to go
deeper your knees are King a vus
collaps okay just rack it just rack
[Music]
it okay you got to arch your
back
like this no Arch the other
way okay you have glutes use
them oh just put it
down okay quit hyperextending your
lumbar
spine God it's almost like you don't
even know how to use your glutes this
hurts my hips quit being a
okay you terrible cor
stability do you even have a TVA your
TVA is so weak it's
pathetic just stop just
stop
wow your rotary stability is
terrible it's almost like you don't have
a multipos I've actually never met
anyone who doesn't have a multifidus
congratulations wow I don't even know
what to say
speechless
okay so this is my neutral spinal
position if I go like this I'm arching
this is actually overarching if I do
this I'm rounding that's that's called
lumbar flexion you don't want to do
spinal flexion you want to stay neutral
so I'm going to pick up this kettle bell
I'm GNA bend down I'm going to grab the
kettle bell I'm not going to be
overarched I'm not going to be rounded
I'm going to be a neutral my head and
neck is also going to be a neutral so
I'm not going to be looking up I won't
be looking down I will stay in neutral
position so I'm going to bend down and
stand up
okay just like that
okay very good next rep I want you to
sit back even
more great form great form one
more all right excellent
job can you imagine how bad that is for
your
body dude your breathing is